Excuse me. My name is Richard Stewart.
I'm a photographer.
May I take a picture of you and your little boy?
What's it for?
It's for a book.
Richard Stewart, 46 Linden Street,
You're writing a book?
It's a book of pictures.
I call it Family Album, U.S.A.
Oh, that's a nice idea.
Well, it's fine if you take our picture.
I'm Martha Vann.
Thank you. I appreciate your help.
I'm Richard. What's your name?
Gerald.
How old are you, Gerald?
Five.
And where do you live?
We live in California.
Well, welcome to New York.
OK, just a second.
I'm almost ready here.
Can I help you?
Oh, please.
Hold Gerald's hand, please. Great!
Now point to the buildings.
Terrific!
Give Mommy a kiss, Gerald. Nice!
Thank you, Gerald.
And thank you, Mrs. Vann.
Oh, my pleasure.
We'll be looking for your book.
Thank you. Good-bye. Bye, Gerald.
Thanks again.
Oh, you're welcome.
Hey, let me take your picture!
Wonderful. Please.
Are you from New York?
No, I'm from Greece.
I'm an exchange student.
When did you come here?
Three months ago.
Your English is very good.
Thanks.
I studied English in school.
Would you like some coffee?
No, thank you.
Tell me about your book.
Oh, it's not finished yet,
but I have some of the pictures.
Would you like to see them?
Yes. I'd like that.
Here they are. Family Album, U.S.A.
It's an album of pictures of the United States:
the cities, the special places, and the people.
And these are pictures of people working:
steelworkers, bankers, police, street vendors,
ambulance drivers, doctors....
Oh, this is my father. He's a doctor.
This is my mother.
What's her name?
Ellen.
My younger brother, Robbie.
He goes to high school.
This is my sister Susan.
She works for a toy company.
Here's my grandfather. He lives in Florida.
And this is my wife Marilyn.
Oh, she's very pretty.
Thanks. And what about your family?
They are in Thessaloniki.
That's a large city in northern Greece.
But now I'm living in the Bronx.
With a Greek-American family?
No. Hispanic.
Oh no! It's five thirty.
Will you excuse me?
I have to meet my wife.
It was nice meeting you.
It was a pleasure meeting you, too.
Thanks for your help.
And good luck! I've got to go.
By the way, I'm Richard.
What's your name?
Alexandra.
Bye-bye, Alexandra. Thanks.
Bye-bye. Richard! Richard! You left your bag!